corante.com 2001-06-03

# C O R A N T E - Tech News. Filtered Daily.

**Information Collection and Use**  
Corante is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. 

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use and analysis. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Sharing**  
We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. Such information enables us to better tailor our content to readers' needs and to help our advertisers better understand the demographics of our audience. Because Corante derives its revenue primarily from advertising, providing such aggregated demographic data is essential to keeping our service free to users. 

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Corante is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Newsletter**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our email newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. We may also ask optional demographic questions such as age, income, education level, and gender. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. Such information, in aggregate, enables us to better tailor our content to readers' needs and helps our advertisers better understand the demographics of our audience. 

Users may have their email addresses removed from the opt-in newsletter subscription at any time by following the instructions printed in the email newsletters. 

**Security**  
This website takes precautions to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, their information is protected both online and off-line. 

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner.We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at:  

Copyright © 2001 Corante. All rights reserved. Terms of use.
